const easyQuestions = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "When was Gangnam Style uploaded to YouTube?",
            "correct_answer": "2012",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "2013",
                "2014",
                "2011"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What Led Zeppelin album contains \"Stairway to Heaven\"?",
            "correct_answer": "Led Zeppelin IV",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Houses of the Holy",
                "Physical Graffiti",
                "Led Zeppelin III"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Who is the lead singer of the British pop rock band Coldplay?",
            "correct_answer": "Chris Martin",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jonny Buckland",
                "Guy Berryman",
                "Will Champion"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "From which country did the song \"Gangnam Style\" originate from?",
            "correct_answer": "South Korea",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Japan",
                "North Korea",
                "China"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "According to the American rapper Nelly, what should you do when its hot in here?",
            "correct_answer": "Take off all your clothes",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Take a cool shower",
                "Drink some water",
                "Go skinny dipping"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which Twitch streamer is the vocalist for Red Vox?",
            "correct_answer": "Vinesauce",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The8BitDrummer",
                "LIRIK",
                "Sodapoppin"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "\"Doctor Jones\", \"Turn Back Time\" and \"Barbie Girl\" were UK number ones for which Eurodance group?",
            "correct_answer": "Aqua",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Vengaboys",
                "Eiffel 65",
                "Sash!"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What is the stage name of English female rapper Mathangi Arulpragasam, who is known for the song \"Paper Planes\"?",
            "correct_answer": "M.I.A.",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "K.I.A.",
                "C.I.A.",
                "A.I.A."
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What is the frontman's name of the metal band Megadeth?",
            "correct_answer": "Dave Mustaine",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Rob Halford",
                "Vince Neil",
                "James Hetfield"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which band recorded the album \"Parallel Lines\"?",
            "correct_answer": "Blondie",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Paramore",
                "Coldplay",
                "The Police"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album 'Flood' in 1990. ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Sting, the lead vocalist of The Police, primarily plays what instrument?",
            "correct_answer": "Bass Guitar",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Drums",
                "Guitar",
                "Keyboards"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which band released songs suchs as \"Rio\", \"Girls on Film\", and \"The Reflex\"?",
            "correct_answer": "Duran Duran",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Cure",
                "New Order",
                "Depeche Mode"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which of these is NOT the name of an album released by English singer-songwriter Adele?",
            "correct_answer": "12",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "19",
                "21",
                "25"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which Canadian reggae musician had a 1993 hit with the song 'Informer'?",
            "correct_answer": "Snow",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Rain",
                "Hail",
                "Sleet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What 1970's American ballad referred to the 1959 plane crash as the \"the day the music died\"?",
            "correct_answer": "American Pie",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kentucky Rain",
                "I Will Always Love You",
                "Rock 'n' Roll Suicide"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "How many strings are there on a cello?",
            "correct_answer": "4",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "5",
                "6",
                "8"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Scatman John's real name was John Paul Larkin.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which of these are NOT a Men at Work song?",
            "correct_answer": "Basket Case",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Dr. Heckyll and Mr. Jive",
                "Who Can It Be Now?",
                "Be Good Johnny"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What album did Bon Iver release in 2016?",
            "correct_answer": "22, A Million",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Bon Iver, Bon Iver",
                "Blood Bank EP",
                "For Emma, Forever Ago"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which rap group released the album \"Straight Outta Compton\"?",
            "correct_answer": "N.W.A",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Wu-Tang Clan",
                "Run-D.M.C.",
                "Beastie Boys"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The \"K\" in \"K-Pop\" stands for which word?",
            "correct_answer": "Korean",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kenyan",
                "Kazakhstan",
                "Kuwaiti"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The \"British Invasion\" was a cultural phenomenon in music where British boy bands became popular in the USA in what decade?",
            "correct_answer": "60's",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "50's",
                "40's",
                "30's"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The Rush song \"YYZ\" derives its name from the IATA aiport identification code for which city?",
            "correct_answer": "Toronto",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Vancouver",
                "Ottawa",
                "Calgary"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which Beatles album does NOT feature any of the band members on it's cover?",
            "correct_answer": "The Beatles (White Album)",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Rubber Soul",
                "Abbey Road",
                "Magical Mystery Tour"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which country does the band Rammstein hail from?",
            "correct_answer": "Germany",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Austria",
                "Armenia",
                "Belgium"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Who is the lead singer of the band Coldplay?",
            "correct_answer": "Chris Martin",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Chris Isaak",
                "Chris Wallace",
                "Chris Connelly"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which artist released the 2012 single \"Harlem Shake\", which was used in numerous YouTube videos in 2013?",
            "correct_answer": "Baauer",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "RL Grime",
                "NGHTMRE",
                "Flosstradamus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "\"Grande Valse\" is a phrase from the song \"Gran Vals\". What is that song segment known as?",
            "correct_answer": "Nokia Tune",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Hello Moto [Motorola Ringtone]",
                "Droid Ringtone",
                "Microsoft Ringtone"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Who had a 1983 hit with the song 'Africa'?",
            "correct_answer": "Toto",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Foreigner",
                "Steely Dan",
                "Journey"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The band Muse released their first album, Showbiz, in what year?",
            "correct_answer": "1999",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "1998",
                "2000",
                "2001"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "According to a song by Belinda Carlisle, Heaven is a place on what?",
            "correct_answer": "Earth",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Venus",
                "Mars",
                "Uranus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The music video to The Buggle's \"Video Killed the Radio Star\" was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which 80s band is fronted by singer/guitarist Robert Smith?",
            "correct_answer": "The Cure",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Smiths",
                "Echo & the Bunnymen",
                "New Order"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "\"The Singing Cowboy\" Gene Autry is credited with the first recording for all but which classic Christmas jingle?",
            "correct_answer": "White Christmas",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Frosty the Snowman",
                "Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
                "Here Comes Santa Claus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "In the  Rossini opera, what was the name of 'The Barber of Seville'?",
            "correct_answer": "Figaro",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Angelo",
                "Fernando",
                "Dave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Brian May was the guitarist for which band?",
            "correct_answer": "Queen",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Pink Floyd",
                "Rolling Stones",
                "The Doors"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Whose signature guitar technique is called the \"windmill\"?",
            "correct_answer": "Pete Townshend",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jimmy Page",
                "Eddie Van Halen",
                "Jimi Hendrix"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What was the name of singer Frank Ocean's second studio album, which was released on August 20, 2016?",
            "correct_answer": "Blonde",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Brunette",
                "Black",
                "Burgundy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "In 2006, which band released their debut album \"A Fever You Can't Sweat Out\"?",
            "correct_answer": "Panic! At the Disco",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Twenty One Pilots",
                "My Chemical Romance",
                "Fall Out Boy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song \"Do the Bartman\".",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Who performed \"I Took A Pill In Ibiza\"?",
            "correct_answer": "Mike Posner",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Avicii",
                "Robbie Williams",
                "Harry Styles"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "The Red Hot Chili Pepper song \"Give It Away\" is from what album?",
            "correct_answer": "Blood Sugar Sex Magik",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "One Hot Minute",
                "By the Way",
                "Stadium Arcadium"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Which famous rapper is featured in Jack Ü (Skrillex and Diplo)'s 2015 single called \"Febreze\"?",
            "correct_answer": "2 Chainz",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kendrick Lamar",
                "Future",
                "Fatman Scoop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "What was Daft Punk's first studio album?",
            "correct_answer": "Homework",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Discovery",
                "Random Access Memories",
                "Human After All"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Who is the frontman of the band 30 Seconds to Mars?",
            "correct_answer": "Jared Leto",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Gerard Way",
                "Matthew Bellamy",
                "Mike Shinoda"
            ]
        }
    ]
}

export default easyQuestions